

Vasilije Simonović

Profile

I have experience working with Python, C#, SQL and MATLAB. As a part of my Masters degree I have participated and developed several projects using Machine learning and Deep learning methods in Python.

I was a professional chess player and I'm good in solving various logical and technical problems.

Work Experience

Freelance jobs – (2020 - present)

Solving mathematics problems, working in Python and Excel (Big data sets, pivot tables etc.);

Consultant – TechPro (2018 - 2020)

Helping with SQL databases and other backend tasks related to websites development;

Loft manager – EPW (July 2018- Sep 2018)

A had a short experience in Netherlands working as a manager in one of the most famous auctions houses in the world for racing pigeons. As racing pigeons are my passion and a hobby it was a great opportunity for me to work and enjoy and to be part of international team.

Education

Faculty of Science - Novi Sad (2016 - 2021 Master Thesis in progress)

Applied mathematics – Big Data (Data science) – MSc

Skills

Python
Excel
ML
DL
AI
MATLAB
Keras
English

SQL

Relevant Coursework:

Large Scale Data Mining, Programing for Data Science, Machine Learning and Pattern Recognition, Big Data in Medicine and Biology, Network science, Databases, Introduction to Image Processing, Graph Theory, Numerical Linear Algebra, Statistics Theory for Machine Learning and Signal Processing

Faculty of Science – Novi Sad (2010 - 2014)

Applied mathematics – Financial mathematics – Bachelor's degree